(upbeat music)
After you pick up your packages for delivery, click View Packages from the Home page in order to
proceed with the actual delivery.
You can select all packages listed or check off one box at a time to mark picked up, then click
the Confirm button.
Confirming a pickup is important for two reasons.
It confirms that you have the packages in your possession in order to proceed to the next step.
And it informs your contact at work that you are delivering the products you picked up.
Now that you have confirmed packages are picked up, you are ready to deliver them and complete the
service they requested.
Communication with your customer is important.
Let's look at the next steps that inform customers that their product is on their way.
From the Job Detail page, send ETA to your customer by clicking Send ETA.
Pick the time and click the text Customer.
The customer immediately receives an ETA notification.
Now you can drive to the customer's location to deliver their product.
When you arrive at the customer's location, click tap to see options.
This action doesn't send the customer a message, it records your arrival time.
Answer the questions and proceed to deliver the product to the customer's room of choice.
Now you can deliver the product to the customer's room of choice.
You'll review the price with the customer and get their approval.
If the customer doesn't approve the price, refer to your company for instructions.
Give the customer your device or follow the updated guidelines that were issued for COVID-19 to
obtain their signature.
Customer clicks review price.
If customer agrees with the price, they click yes.
Customer will need to sign and click done.
After they click done, a thank you page appears.
Customer hands you the phone.
Once you're at your vehicle, click complete job to take a selfie.
For safety purposes, you must take the selfie photo at your vehicle.
A selfie confirms that the person who was assigned the job completed the job.
Click take photo.
Take your selfie and submit it.
The task is complete.
This completes the delivery.
On the home page, you will see a successful completion notification.
The task will no longer display.
Your next delivery displays in the queue.
You'll repeat the same steps for each new delivery.